## VICKIE QIWEI HE

#### CONTACT

143 Tampines street 12, Singapore 520143

81017196

hxxpopo@gmail.com

My Portfolio (password: aioi) : <a href="http://vickiehe.xyz">http://vickiehe.xyz</a>

#### EDUCATION

# BACHELOR DEGREE IN MASS COMMUNICATION WITH ADVERTISING

Northumbria University – 2014 - 2016

### DIPLOMA IN MULTIMEDIA & ANIMATION

Ngee Ann Polytechnic 2010 - 2013

#### SKILLS

- Adobe family
- Figma, XD
- Cinema 4D, Spline 3D
- Jira, Lark

#### PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

An organized and creative professional with proven design skills and a desire to learn more. 7+ years of experience working as a designer for a diverse variety of organization and clients. Gained expertise in UI/UX design and visual design. Currently looking for a position with an organization where I can utilize my existing skills set and knowledge to increase company profitability.

#### EXPERIENCE

#### **Senior Product Designer**

OKX | 2023 - 10/2023 | Crypto exchange

OKX is a global cryptocurrency spot and derivatives exchange and the second biggest crypto exchange by trading volume, serving over 50 million people globally.

- Work closely with business stakeholders and product team, support the product development process with wireframes, user flows, journey maps, high-fidelity mockups, interactive prototypes, and evaluative researches.
- Proven track record of managing all aspects of a successful product launch throughout its lifecycle. Adept at translating product strategy into detailed requirements and prototypes.
- Generate product roadmaps and secure consensus from stakeholders on scope and deliverable timelines.

#### **Expert UI/UX Designer**

Shopee/SeaMoney Pte Ltd | 2021 – 2023 | Digital Banking

SeaMoney is a part of Sea Group, a leading global consumer internet company, offering mobile wallet services, payment processing, credit offerings, and related digital financial services and products.

 Work closely with business stakeholders and product team, design 0-1 consumer banking products for Southeast Asia customers with different needs, including user research, overall user flows, wireframes, interactive prototypes, and high-fidelity designs.

#### EXTRA

- Japanese N3 level
- Photography

#### REFERENCES

#### Faith

AVP

CapitaLand Singapore Limited faithsoh@capitaland.com

#### **Denys**

AVP

DBS Bank Ltd denyskutsevalov@dbs.com

#### **Donald**

Head of Design
Shopee/SeaMoney Pte Ltd
Donald.linhy@shopee.com

#### Winnie

Senior Designer OKBL Pte Ltd 8697 7924

#### EXPERIENCE (CONTINUED)

- Collaborate with developers and QA team to conduct user acceptance testing to ensure product quality and best user experience.
- Responsible for design language system and design asset library which includes editable templates, 3D and 2D assets.

#### **Product Designer**

DBS Bank Ltd | 2019 - 2021 | Banking

DBS Bank Ltd is a Singaporean multinational banking and financial services corporation headquartered in Marina Bay, Singapore.

- Work closely with business stakeholders, design corporate banking products for Singapore and Hong Kong users.
- Collaborate with developers and QA team to conduct user acceptance testing to ensure product quality and best user experience...
- Support research team and conduct user research / user interview to identify user needs and monitor user behaviour, continuously improving the user experience.
- Work closely with design system team and define design standard for DBS design library.

#### **Design Executive**

CapitaLand Singapore Limited | 2016 - 2018 | Real estate

CapitaLand Limited is a Singaporean multinational alternative asset management company focusing on real estate, infrastructure and private equity.

- UI/UX design for CapitaLand's corporate/consumer loyalty program
- Designed & crafted marketing & e-marketing materials on a range of projects, for brochures and advertisements; ensured uniformity in the brand language for the promotional brands
- Improved products by analyzing customer database and user surveys to identify user pain points
- Initiated a series of integrated marketing campaigns including email, print, digital, outdoor and spending analysis.